Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XCIV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XCV is arranged in 13 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XCIV. GRAND PRESIDENT'S MONTHLY BULLETIN
  - Sub-Series 470-0. Grand President's Monthly Bulletin
    - General, 1958-1959 (Box 605a, Folder 1)
      June 1958-October 1959.
    - General, 1958 (Box 605a, Folder 2)
      March-May 1958.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 605a, Folder 3)
      October 18, 1957-February 1958.
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 605a, Folder 4)
    - General, 1959-1962 (Box 605a, Folder 5)
      November 1959-62.
    - General, 1957 (Box 605a, Folder 6)
      May 23, 1957-October 17, 1957.
    - General, 1957 (Box 605a, Folder 7)
      January 1957-May 22, 1957.
    - General, 1956 (Box 605a, Folder 8)
      July-December 1956.
    - General, 1956 (Box 605a, Folder 9)
      March-June 1956.
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 605a, Folder 10)
      February 1955-February 1956.
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 605a, Folder 11)
      February 1954-January 1955.
- Series XCV. HOSPITAL ASSOCIATIONS
  - Sub-Series 474-0. Hospital Associations. General
    - Study, 1951 (Box 605a, Folder 12-13)
    - General, 1950-1951 (Box 605b, Folder 1)
      April 1950-August 1951.
    - General, 1950 (Box 605b, Folder 2)
      January 27, 1950-March 1950.
    - General, 1949-1950 (Box 605b, Folder 3)
      November 9, 1949-January 26, 1950.
    - General, 1949 (Box 605b, Folder 4)
      September 1949-November 8, 1949.
    - General, 1948-1949 (Box 605b, Folder 5)
      August 1948-August 1949.
    - General, 1946-1948 (Box 605b, Folder 6)
      September 1946-July 1948.
    - General, 1942-1945 (Box 605b, Folder 7)
    - General, 1938-1941 (Box 605b, Folder 8)
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 606a, Folder 1)
      April 1958-62.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 606a, Folder 2)
      1957-March 1958.
    - Blue Cross, 1951-1959 (Box 606a, Folder 3)
    - Replies to Letter Dated April 17, 1958 (Box 606a, Folder 4)
    - Financial Statements Used in Making Study of Hospital Associations., 1949-1950 (Box 606a, Folder 5)
    - Survey on Company Contributions to Hospital Associations., 1949-1950 (Box 606a, Folder 6)
    - September 1951-1956 (Box 606a, Folder 7)
    - Hospital Association Survey, 1949 (Box 606b, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospital Association Survey, 1949-1950 (Box 606b, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 474-2. Hospital Associations. Illinois Central Hospital Association
    - General, 1947-1957 (Box 606b, Folder 4)
    - Case No. A-883, 1940-1946 (Box 606b, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 474-13. Hospital Associations. Central of Georgia Hospital Association
    - General, 1952-1962 (Box 606b, Folder 6)
      1952-May 1962.
  - Sub-Series 474-15. Hospital Associations. Santa Fe Coast Lines Hospital Association
    - General, 1940-1946 (Box 606b, Folder 7)
    - Case No. A-2691, 1947-1948 (Box 606b, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-2428, 1946 (Box 606b, Folder 9)
    - Brochure, 1946 (Box 606b, Folder 10)
      1946 March 15
  - Sub-Series 474-18. Hospital Associations. Southern Pacific, Pacific Lines Hospital Association
    - General, 1946-1957 (Box 606b, Folder 11)
    - Mrs. Hansen, 1956-1960 (Box 607a, Folder 1)
      November 1956-60.
    - 474-18. Hospital Associations. Southern Pacific, Pacific Lines Hospital Association, 1945-1946 (Box 607a, Folder 2)
      April 1945-June 1946.
    - Case No. A-1653, 1943-1945 (Box 607a, Folder 3)
      1943-March 1945.
  - Sub-Series 474-19. Hospital Associations. Union Pacific Hospital Association
    - General, 1948-1955 (Box 607a, Folder 4)
    - General, 1947 (Box 607a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 474-23. Hospital Associations. Texas and Pacific Hospital Association
    - General, 1948-1962 (Box 607a, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 474-26. Hospital Associations. North Carolina and St. Louis Hospital Association
    - General, 1946-1949 (Box 607a, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 474-40. Hospital Associations. Southern Pacific Lines in Texas and Louisiana
    - Texas and New Orleans Hospital Association. Case No. A-2098, 1945-1953 (Box 607a, Folder 8)
      August 1945-53.
    - Texas and New Orleans Hospital Association, 1939-1945 (Box 607a, Folder 9)
      1939-July 1945.
  - Sub-Series 474-54. Hospital Associations. Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Hospital Association
    - General, 1942-1949 (Box 607b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 474-78. Hospital Associations. Colorado and Southern Hospital Association
    - General, 1949 (Box 607b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 474-84. Hospital Associations. Missouri Pacific Hospital Association
    - General, 1960-1963 (Box 607b, Folder 3)
      July 20, 1960-63.
    - General, 1958-1960 (Box 607b, Folder 4)
      September 1958-July 19, 1960.
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 607b, Folder 5)
      May 1957-August 1958.
    - General, 1954-1957 (Box 607b, Folder 6)
      1954-April 1957.
    - General, 1951-1953 (Box 607b, Folder 7)
    - General, 1944-1950 (Box 607b, Folder 8)
    - General, 1915-1944 (Box 607b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 474-157. Hospital Associations. Wabash Hospital Association
    - General, 1951-1961 (Box 607b, Folder 10)